{
    "id": "0cc73525ab1d496cb420da2f695af842",
    "title": "Adverb clause of comparison",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7423e69837384fa0a5da1e9df3f525a6",
            "title": "Adverb Clause Of Comparison",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She is older than ................................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "him"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She looks older than ..............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "her",
                        "she is",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He earns more money ............................................... me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "then"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am ............................................. than you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more strong",
                        "stronger"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are ................................................... than our neighbors.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "richer",
                        "the richer",
                        "the richest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ............................................. than her sisters.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "prettiest",
                        "prettier"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He runs ................................................... than you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "faster",
                        "more fast"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is .............................................. stupid as he is lazy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "as",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Nobody loves you more than .............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "me",
                        "I",
                        "I do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I earn more than ............................................ does.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "him"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}